{"_id":{"$oid":"57dc2e0d9b2e788645d2c816"},"qname":"Question 1","qnum":1,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"What is an IS/IT Incident?","choice":["Clash of two Desktops on the highway.","Clash of a Desktop and a Notebook on the highway.","Slipping and falling  IT Expert ","Sending an e-mail to wrong person.","An incident is an unplanned interruption to an IT service or reduction in the quality of an IT service."],"answer":"An incident is an unplanned interruption to an IT service or reduction in the quality of an IT service."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57dc687b9b2e788645d2c817"},"qname":"Question 2","qnum":2,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"What is Incident Management and how does it apply to our team?","choice":["Incident Management is informing vendors for outage in service.","Incident Management is handling lifecycle of incident from opening till closure.","None of the above."],"answer":"Incident Management is handling lifecycle of incident from opening till closure."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57dd98799b2e788645d2c818"},"qname":"Question 3","qnum":3,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"What is the primary objective of Incident Management?","choice":["To manage incidents.","To understand incidents","To return the IT service to users as quickly as possible.","To keep statistics of incidents","To log incidents"],"answer":"To return the IT service to users as quickly as possible."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57dd98c99b2e788645d2c819"},"qname":"Question 4","qnum":4,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"What is the last process step in Incident Management? ","choice":["Detection","Recording","Classification","Investigation and Diagnosis","Resolution and Recovery","Closure"],"answer":"Closure"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57dd9a1b9b2e788645d2c81a"},"qname":"Question 5","qnum":5,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"What other processes can Incident Management be an input to? ","choice":["Problem Management and Change Management","Problem Management and Release Management","Change Management and Release Management","Problem Management and Configuration Management","None of the above"],"answer":"Problem Management and Change Management"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57dd9bad9b2e788645d2c81b"},"qname":"Question 6","qnum":6,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"When we request for Authorized End Users to do certain workarounds, it falls under which process step?","choice":["Investigation and Diagnosis","Resolution and Recovery","Classification","Detection","Recording"],"answer":"Resolution and Recovery"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57dd9c669b2e788645d2c81c"},"qname":"Question 7","qnum":7,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"When setting an Incident Ticket to “Waiting for Other Party”, does the RTO or SLA counter stop?","choice":["Yes. There is nothing we can do.","No."],"answer":"No."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57dd9cda9b2e788645d2c81d"},"qname":"Question 8","qnum":8,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"When an Incident is tagged as P1 or P2, our team must inform and work closely with whom?","choice":["End User","Country Manager","Area CIO","Group CIO","Incident Manager"],"answer":"Incident Manager"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddb8689b2e788645d2c81e"},"qname":"Question 9","qnum":9,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"Which one is not a trigger for Escalation?","choice":["Degree of severity of an Incident","Duration of resolution","Status Inquiry by end user"],"answer":"Status Inquiry by end user"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddb9429b2e788645d2c81f"},"qname":"Question 10","qnum":10,"Quiz":"Incident  Management","question":"Who is/are in charge of updating the Incident Record? ","choice":["Authorized End User","First Level Support","Support Specialist","Incident Manager","None of the above"],"answer":"First Level Support"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbadb9b2e788645d2c820"},"qname":"Question 11","qnum":11,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"It is difficult to remember each password that we have, in this situation what could be a good strategy?","choice":["I save all my different passwords in a file: when I need one, I can easily retrieve it.","I still prefer to use a different password each time.","I use the same password for each service that I use."],"answer":"I still prefer to use a different password each time."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbb419b2e788645d2c821"},"qname":"Question 12","qnum":12,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"Who are hackers?","choice":["They are benign computer experts.","They are malicious computer criminals.","Hackers could be both benign and criminal programmers."],"answer":"Hackers could be both benign and criminal programmers."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbb979b2e788645d2c822"},"qname":"Question 13","qnum":13,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"Why updating and patching computer operating systems is important:","choice":["Fixes problems and makes the operating system more secure.","It makes me pay more for the software I use.","Improves the working functions of my operating system."],"answer":"Fixes problems and makes the operating system more secure."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbbf49b2e788645d2c823"},"qname":"Question 14","qnum":14,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"What is your perspective about the need for updating the antivirus?","choice":["I have never been a victim of malware. These updates are not relevant to me.","The antivirus update protects my computer from newly created malware.","The antivirus updates ensure the correct performance of my computer."],"answer":"The antivirus update protects my computer from newly created malware."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbc539b2e788645d2c824"},"qname":"Question 15","qnum":15,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"When you open the email the text says ‘Please click here http://shorl.jh.com, there is surprise for you’. What would you do in such scenario?","choice":["You call your friend before doing anything with the e-mail.","You click on the link to see the surprise.","You decide not to click on the link."],"answer":"You call your friend before doing anything with the e-mail."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbcb49b2e788645d2c825"},"qname":"Question 16","qnum":16,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"How can botnets affect your computer?","choice":["Botnets are a form of malicious software.","Someone could take control of my computer and use it as part of a botnet","I might not be able to use an on-line service if it is affected by a botnet."],"answer":"Someone could take control of my computer and use it as part of a botnet"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbd219b2e788645d2c826"},"qname":"Question 17","qnum":17,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"Cookies raise some security and privacy concerns, for example:","choice":["They could contain a virus which then infects my computer.","Getting Fat","The collection of my private information","The collection of private information as well as the risk that someone could impersonate me"],"answer":"The collection of private information as well as the risk that someone could impersonate me"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbd8e9b2e788645d2c827"},"qname":"Question 18","qnum":18,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"What does social engineering mean in a security context?","choice":["Building systems that are easy to use for society.","It is a form of social deception focussed on information gathering, fraud, or system access.","Someone has knowledge of your personal details and is using them to their own advantage."],"answer":"It is a form of social deception focussed on information gathering, fraud, or system access."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbde09b2e788645d2c828"},"qname":"Question 19","qnum":19,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"In order to protect your communication over these public networks you always…","choice":["Use the private browsing function of your browser.","Use a Virtual Private Network or VPN.","Turn off your device’s file sharing function."],"answer":"Use a Virtual Private Network or VPN."}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbe2b9b2e788645d2c829"},"qname":"Question 20","qnum":20,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"What is the popular name which was given to the fatal programming error in OpenSSL in 2014?","choice":["Heartbleed","Zeus","Koobface"],"answer":"Heartbleed"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"57ddbe779b2e788645d2c82a"},"qname":"Question 21","qnum":21,"Quiz":"IT Security","question":"What a ‘Trojan Horse’ ?","choice":["It is a computer virus that frequently attack computers.","It is a malicious software that allows other programs to control your computer.","It is a malfunction of the software that makes it difficult to navigate the Internet."],"answer":"It is a malicious software that allows other programs to control your computer."}
